{
    "subject": "resource/The_Legend_of_Bagger_Vance",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Jake_Eberts",
    "human_readable": "The Legend of Bagger Vance was produced by Jake Eberts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9566711187362671,
            "question": "Jake Eberts is credited with what role in the making of 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9381580948829651,
            "question": "Besides 'The Legend of Bagger Vance', what other films might Jake Eberts have produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065423607826233,
            "question": "What was Jake Eberts' contribution to the movie 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8911546468734741,
            "question": "What type of work did Jake Eberts do on 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8888314366340637,
            "question": "Who produced the movie 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116599917411804,
            "question": "Can you tell me who was involved in producing 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7666206359863281,
            "question": "What is the name of the film producer who worked on 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7503341436386108,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Jake Eberts."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5897502899169922,
            "question": "Who was responsible for bringing 'The Legend of Bagger Vance' to the screen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5040319561958313,
            "question": "Is Jake Eberts known for producing any famous movies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Legend of Bagger Vance was produced by Jake Eberts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5089_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was responsible for bringing 'The Legend of Bagger Vance' to the screen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5089_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film produced by Jake Eberts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5089_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film producer who worked on 'The Legend of Bagger Vance'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5089_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5089_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text explicitly states that Jake Eberts is one of the producers of \"The Legend of Bagger Vance\".  You can find this in several documents listed. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Jake Eberts being a producer for The Legend of Bagger Vance."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Jake Eberts is one of the producers for \"The Legend of Bagger Vance,\" which supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}